Guide to the Archives Union File (AUF), Section 8: Boxes 443-506
Archives Union File (AUF), Section 8: Boxes 443-506
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations)., Publication (Box 479, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: The North American Free Trade Agreement - How U.S. taxpayers subsidize the transfer of jobs to Mexico -- #27, 29, 1993- 1994 (Box 479, Folder 2)
    Notes: Article. 2 copies.
  - Item 4: Uruguay round of the GATT: persistent trade deficits, 1994; Publication (Box 479, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: Structure of the AFL-CIO, Publication (Box 479, Folder 2)
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations)., Publication (Box 479, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Danger ahead: negotiating for retiree health care benefits, Publication (Box 479, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: We just come to work: we don't come to die, Publication (Box 479, Folder 3)
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations)., Publication (Box 479, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Inflation 1979: an analysis with suggested solutions: a report, Publication (Box 479, Folder 4)
    Author: Research Department
  - Item 2: The trade picture year end 1987, 1988; Publication (Box 479, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: Multilateral trade agreements: AFL-CIO analysis & recommendations on non-tariff issues, 1979; Publication (Box 479, Folder 4)
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations)., Publication (Box 479, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Reinvigorating the public service, 1992; Publication (Box 479, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: The Health and welfare plan of the nation's railroads and the railway labor organizations, 1977; Publication (Box 479, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: Group Insurance Plan: Officers and Employees, 1979; Publication (Box 479, Folder 5)
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations)., Publication (Box 479, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Public employees bargain for excellence, 1995; Publication (Box 479, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: Issues & Answers, 1992; Publication (Box 479, Folder 6)
    Notes: Jan, July, Sept. (1992)
  - Item 3: Issues & Answers, 1993; Publication (Box 479, Folder 6)
    Notes: May (1993)
  - Item 4: Issues & Answers, 1994; Publication (Box 479, Folder 6)
    Notes: Jan., Mar., Apr., July-Aug (1994)
  - Item 5: Issues & Answers, 1995; Publication (Box 479, Folder 6)
    Notes: Mar/Apr, Aug, Nov. (1995)
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations)., Publication (Box 479, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Labor champion of public education, 1986; Publication (Box 479, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: Strategies to help the working poor, 1990; Publication (Box 479, Folder 7)
  - Item 3: Tell Congress before it's too late, Publication (Box 479, Folder 7)
  - Item 4: PED Executive Board Criticizes Ford on New York City, 1975; Publication (Box 479, Folder 7)
  - Item 5: Issues & Answers, 1989; Publication (Box 479, Folder 7)
    Notes: July, Sept.-Oct., Dec. (1989)
  - Item 6: Issues & Answers, 1990; Publication (Box 479, Folder 7)
    Notes: Jan., Mar.-Apr., Sept. (1990)
  - Item 7: Issues & Answers, 1991; Publication (Box 479, Folder 7)
    Notes: Jan., Mar., July, Dec. (1991)
  - Item 8: Issues & Answers, 1992; Publication (Box 479, Folder 7)
    Notes: Mar.-Apr., June (1992)
  - Item 9: Fact versus fiction; (article), 1992; Publication (Box 479, Folder 7)
  - Item 10: Economic comparisons between open shop states and free collective bargaining states, 1990; Publication (Box 479, Folder 7)
  - Item 11: Blacks in the workforce, 1990; Publication (Box 479, Folder 7)
  - Item 12: The Pocketbook issues, 1990; Publication (Box 479, Folder 7)
  - Item 13: Together in solidarity, 1983; Publication (Box 479, Folder 7)
  - Item 14: Hispanics in the workforce, 1988-1989 (Box 479, Folder 7)
  - Item 15: Why unions?, 1988-1989 (Box 479, Folder 7)
  - Item 16: Not far enough: the Budget Act of 1990, 1991; Publication (Box 479, Folder 7)
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations)., Publication (Box 480, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Constitution of the Union Label and Service Trades Department of the American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations - Serial -, 1987; Publication (Box 480, Folder 1)
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations)., Publication (Box 480, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Keeping a healthy credit rating, Publication (Box 480, Folder 2)
    Author: Union Privilege Benefit Programs
  - Item 2: Union Member Mortgage, Publication (Box 480, Folder 2)
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations)., Publication (Box 480, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: On Saturday April 28, 1990, the AFL-CIO will once again observe Workers Memorial Day, Publication (Box 480, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Union Yes, 1991; Publication (Box 480, Folder 3)
    Notes: Spring edition (1991)
  - Item 3: Union Yes, 1995; Publication (Box 480, Folder 3)
    Notes: Summer edition (1995)
  - Item 4: Union Yes: Labor voting record, 1987-1988 (Box 480, Folder 3)
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations)., Publication (Box 480, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Workers Memorial Day - Safe jobs. It's our right (flyer), 1991; Publication (Box 480, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Safe Jobs. It's our Right, 1991; Publication (Box 480, Folder 4)
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations)., Publication (Box 480, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Rules governing AFL-CIO state central bodies, 1973; Publication (Box 480, Folder 5)
    Notes: c. 2
  - Item 2: Rules governing AFL-CIO state central bodies, 1978; Publication (Box 480, Folder 5)
- Alabama State, AFL-CIO, Publication (Box 480, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Constitution and by-laws [of] Alabama Labor Council, AFL-CIO and Alabama Committee on Political Education, AFL-CIO., 1972; Publication (Box 480, Folder 6)
    Author: Labor Council
- Arizona State, AFL-CIO., Publication (Box 480, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Constitution and bylaws, 1974; Publication (Box 480, Folder 7)
- Arkansas State, AFL-CIO., Publication (Box 480, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Officers' Report, 1975; Publication (Box 480, Folder 8)
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations)., Publication (Box 480, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Force for progress, 1995; Publication (Box 480, Folder 9)
    Author: California Labor Federation
- California Labor Council on Political Education, Publication (Box 480, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Constitution, rules and order of business, California Labor Council on Political Education, adopted by the California Labor COPE Convention, San Francisco, December 3, 1970, Publication (Box 480, Folder 10)
- California Labor Council on Political Education, Publication (Box 480, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Proceedings and reports, ... pre-primary election convention, California Labor COPE, 1982; Publication (Box 480, Folder 11)
  - Item 2: Proceedings: COPE Pre-General Election Convention (1982) -- Serial, Publication (Box 480, Folder 11)
- California Labor Federation, AFL-CIO, Publication (Box 480, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Constitution: Rules and order of business - 1986, 1990, 1994 (Serial), 1986-1994 (Box 480, Folder 12)
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations)., Publication (Box 480, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Constitution, 1975; Publication (Box 480, Folder 13)
    Author: Colorado Labor Council
- Connecticut State, AFL-CIO, Publication (Box 480, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Constitution, 1980; Publication (Box 480, Folder 14)
- Connecticut State, AFL-CIO, Publication (Box 480, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Vital links: a handbook for Connecticut local central bodies' officers and delegates, 1985; Publication (Box 480, Folder 15)
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations)., Publication (Box 480, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Constitution and by-laws, 1974; Publication (Box 480, Folder 16)
    Author: Deleware State Labor Council
- Florida State. AFL-CIO, Publication (Box 480, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Constitution and by-laws, 1975; Publication (Box 480, Folder 17)
- Georgia State AFL-CIO, Publication (Box 480, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Constitution and by-laws, 1975; Publication (Box 480, Folder 18)
- Idaho State AFL-CIO, Publication (Box 480, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Constitution, 1976; Publication (Box 480, Folder 19)
  - Item 2: Constitution, 1977; Publication (Box 480, Folder 19)
- Illinois State Federation of Labor, Publication (Box 480, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Constitution, 1971; Publication (Box 480, Folder 20)
- Illinois State Federation of Labor, Publication (Box 480, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: A Union representative's manual on occupational disease, 1983; Publication (Box 480, Folder 21)
  - Item 2: Final Resolutions, 1992; Publication (Box 480, Folder 21)
  - Item 3: Final Resolutions, 1994; Publication (Box 480, Folder 21)
- Illinois State Federation of Labor, Publication (Box 481, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: memo - The Illinoisand Congress of Industrial Organizations is composed of approximately 2500 local unions, city central bodies, councils and Statewide Organizations, Publication (Box 481, Folder 1)
- Illinois State AFL-CIO. Department of Central Management Services, Publication (Box 481, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Agreement, 1979; Publication (Box 481, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Agreement, 1981; Publication (Box 481, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Agreement, 1986; Publication (Box 481, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: Agreement, 1989; Publication (Box 481, Folder 2)
- Illinois State AFL-CIO, Publication (Box 481, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Constitution, 1958; Publication (Box 481, Folder 3)
- Iowa Federation of Labor, AFL-CIO, Publication (Box 481, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Constitution and by-laws, 1976; Publication (Box 481, Folder 4)
- Kansas State Federation of Labor, Publication (Box 481, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Constitution and by-laws, Publication (Box 481, Folder 5)
- Kentucky State AFL-CIO, Publication (Box 481, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Constitution, 1984; Publication (Box 481, Folder 6)
    Notes: Photocopy
- Louisiana State AFL-CIO, Publication (Box 481, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Constitution, 1975; Publication (Box 481, Folder 7)
- Maine AFL-CIO, Publication (Box 481, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Constitution, 1974; Publication (Box 481, Folder 8)
- Massachusetts State Labor Council, AFL-CIO., Publication (Box 481, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Constitution, 1975; Publication (Box 481, Folder 9)
- Michigan State AFL-CIO, Publication (Box 481, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Constitution, 1976; Publication (Box 481, Folder 10)
- Mississippi AFL-CIO, Publication (Box 481, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Constitution, 1972; Publication (Box 481, Folder 11)
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations)., Publication (Box 481, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Constitution, Publication (Box 481, Folder 12)
    Author: Missouri State Labor Council
- Nebraska State AFL-CIO, Publication (Box 481, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Constitution, 1983; Publication (Box 481, Folder 13)
- Nevada State AFL-CIO, Publication (Box 481, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Constitution, 1971; Publication (Box 481, Folder 14)
- New Hampshire State Labor Council, Publication (Box 481, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Constitution, 1974; Publication (Box 481, Folder 15)
- New Jersey State AFL-CIO, Publication (Box 481, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Constitution, 1988; Publication (Box 481, Folder 16)
  - Item 2: Constitution, 1990; Publication (Box 481, Folder 16)
  - Item 3: Constitution, 1992; Publication (Box 481, Folder 16)
- New Jersey State AFL-CIO, Publication (Box 481, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Legislative Bulletin, 1978; Publication (Box 481, Folder 17)
    Notes: Mar., June (1978)
  - Item 2: Legislative Bulletin, 1979; Publication (Box 481, Folder 17)
    Notes: Feb. (1979)
  - Item 3: Legislative Bulletin, 1989; Publication (Box 481, Folder 17)
    Notes: June (1989)
  - Item 4: Legislative Bulletin, 1991; Publication (Box 481, Folder 17)
    Notes: May-June (1991)
- New Jersey State AFL-CIO, Publication (Box 481, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: A-2616-Charity Care-Health Plan Bankruptcies, 1994-1995 (Box 481, Folder 18)
  - Item 2: COPE/Legislative Conference, 1995; Publication (Box 481, Folder 18)
    Notes: January 3-5, 1995. Correspondence
  - Item 3: President's report, 1995; Publication (Box 481, Folder 18)
    Notes: January 17, 1995. Correspondence
  - Item 4: Boycott of Wal-Mart, Sam's, B.J.'s Warehouse, Costco, Weis Market, K-Mart, IKEA, 1994-1995 (Box 481, Folder 18)
  - Item 5: S-1348 TDI Theft, 1994-1995 (Box 481, Folder 18)
  - Item 6: COPE, 1994-1995 (Box 481, Folder 18)
  - Item 7: U.S. Senator Lautenberg Campaign, 1994-1995 (Box 481, Folder 18)
  - Item 8: Local 827 IBEW State Telephone Workers are in a battle with Telecommunications, Inc., 1994; Publication (Box 481, Folder 18)
  - Item 9: The union built amusement park in Jackson, NJ - Six Flags Great Adventure - has offered discount coupons, 1994; Publication (Box 481, Folder 18)
  - Item 10: Shortly the next round of grant applications will be going out for the "Youth Transitions to Work Partnership Act"..., 1994; Publication (Box 481, Folder 18)
  - Item 11: Legislative Conference - Oct. 18-19-20, 1994 Trump Plaza Casino Hotel, Publication (Box 481, Folder 18)
  - Item 12: The Division of Labor, 1994; Publication (Box 481, Folder 18)
  - Item 13: Labor Round Table, 1994; Publication (Box 481, Folder 18)
  - Item 14: Correspondence - Due to the 'gamesmanship' being practiced by both parties in the Legislature, we are finding it increasingly difficult to establish; For the first time in many years the entertaining and informative AFL-CIO Union-Industries Show is being, 1986-1987 (Box 481, Folder 18)
  - Item 15: Correspondence - The 10 General Presidents listed on the enclosed sheet have requested us to contract our affiliates for support of three agenecies that employ significant; Update on the theft of worker contributions to U.I funds to pay for charity care, 1996; Publication (Box 481, Folder 18)
  - Item 16: Official Convention Call - Twenty-first convention; Eighteenth Convention, 1982-1988 (Box 481, Folder 18)
  - Item 17: Correspondence - Legislative/COPE Conference -- 5/31-6/1 and 6/2/94, 1994; Publication (Box 481, Folder 18)
  - Item 18: List of Executive Officers, Executive Board Members, Affiliated Local Unions, Principal Officers of Affiliated Unions, Total Membership of Affiliated Unions, Delegate Entitlement of Affiliated Unions, Publication (Box 481, Folder 18)
  - Item 19: Legislative Conference and Labor/Management Health Care cost containment conference (1984), Publication (Box 481, Folder 18)
- New Jersey State AFL-CIO, Publication (Box 481, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: AFL-CIO Scholarship for explorer scouts, 1994-1996 (Box 481, Folder 19)
  - Item 2: Please look over the enclosed news story of the Executive Board's 7/13/94 trip to Washington, 1994-1996 (Box 481, Folder 19)
  - Item 3: Enclosed please find the hotel reservation form for our upcoming Legislative/COPE Conference being held on, 1994-1996 (Box 481, Folder 19)
  - Item 4: s Labor losing its swat?, 1994-1996 (Box 481, Folder 19)
  - Item 5: We have put together a political action plan for NJ..., 1994-1996 (Box 481, Folder 19)
  - Item 6: S-1348 TDI theft, 1995-1996 (Box 481, Folder 19)
  - Item 7: Unions smashed by business and government, 1995-1996 (Box 481, Folder 19)
  - Item 8: Urgent: Governor's budget steals from workers, 1995-1996 (Box 481, Folder 19)
  - Item 9: Steel Industry under new attack, 1995-1996 (Box 481, Folder 19)
  - Item 10: Cocktail party honoring Senator Kosco, 1995-1996 (Box 481, Folder 19)
  - Item 11: Theft of Workers' unemployment contributions to fund charity care, 1995-1996 (Box 481, Folder 19)
  - Item 12: Advertisement solicitations from the New Jersey Labor Journal, 1995-1996 (Box 481, Folder 19)
  - Item 13: COPE Assembly endorsements, 1995-1996 (Box 481, Folder 19)
  - Item 14: 1st Official Convention call 4/21-24, 1996 and Legislative Report, 1995-1996 (Box 481, Folder 19)
  - Item 15: The issue of hospital Charity Care costs for all 80 hospitals statewide combined averages $400 million per year, 1995- 1996 (Box 481, Folder 19)
  - Item 16: Reschedule of 24th Constitutional Convention, 1995-1996 (Box 481, Folder 19)
  - Item 17: Votes on privatizing motor vehicle and K O of Passaic Flood Tunnel, 1995-1996 (Box 481, Folder 19)
  - Item 18: A-265/S-1961 corrects the 'lag' time problem with collecting unemployment benefits, 1995-1996 (Box 481, Folder 19)
  - Item 19: Legislative/COPE Conference: Sept. 18-20, 1995, Publication (Box 481, Folder 19)
  - Item 20: Yesterday we were jotified by the Washington, D.C. AFL-CIO that Republican Congressmen Bob Franks, Frank Lo Biondo, Bill Marinin, Chris Smith and Congresswoman Marge Roukema stood tall and voted NOT to repeal section 13C..., 1994-1995 (Box 481, Folder 19)
  - Item 21: Hotel Reservation Form, 1994-1995 (Box 481, Folder 19)
  - Item 22: Bankrupting the workers unemployment insurance fund, 1994-1995 (Box 481, Folder 19)
  - Item 23: Carrier Foundation - Union Health Administrators, 1994-1995 (Box 481, Folder 19)
  - Item 24: It is with great pleasure that we are able to announce that Tuesday, Aug. 22, 1995, Gov. Christie Whitman signed into law an important labor bill that extends unemployment benefits, Publication (Box 481, Folder 19)
  - Item 25: Three items - #1 Workers' comp, #2 20% State reduction in hospital reimbursement, #3 Carrier Clinic settled by boycott, 1994- 1995 (Box 481, Folder 19)
  - Item 26: On Thurs. Dec. 15, 1994, the NJ Senate dealth the trade union movement a dirty low down blow, Publication (Box 481, Folder 19)
  - Item 27: U.C. adding lag quarters to benefits, 1994-1995 (Box 481, Folder 19)
  - Item 28: The horrible tragedy that happened in Oklanhoma City last week brings into sharp focus just how vulnerable working men and women are as they perfomr their daily lives, 1994-1995 (Box 481, Folder 19)
  - Item 29: Local union membership voter lists on their way, 1994-1995 (Box 481, Folder 19)
  - Item 30: Candidates - Question #2 - Take 5 program ..., 1994-1995 (Box 481, Folder 19)
  - Item 31: The announcement was made at our Legislative/COPE Conference on May 23-24 at the Showboat Casino-Hotel in Atlantic City, 1994- 1995 (Box 481, Folder 19)
  - Item 32: OSHA training program courses available to all unions upon request, 1994-1995 (Box 481, Folder 19)
  - Item 33: Union summer program, 1994-1995 (Box 481, Folder 19)
  - Item 34: Worker's memorial day, 1994-1995 (Box 481, Folder 19)
  - Item 35: United Way and the AFL-CIO, 1994-1995 (Box 481, Folder 19)
  - Item 36: Legislative Conference Jan. 3-4-5, 1995 Trump Plaza Hotel, Publication (Box 481, Folder 19)
  - Item 37: Health Status, 1994-1995 (Box 481, Folder 19)
  - Item 38: The New Jersey State AFL-CIO will hold its Fifth Annual Labor Awards Dinner..., 1994-1995 (Box 481, Folder 19)
  - Item 39: For the past year and a half the Workforce Development Partnership (WPD) Act has been in existence., 1994-1995 (Box 481, Folder 19)
  - Item 40: Enclosed is the late delivery of the hotel reservation form for the Jan. 3-5, 1995 Mid-winter conference, 1994-1995 (Box 481, Folder 19)
- New Jersey State AFL-CIO, Publication (Box 482, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Correspondence, 1968-1970 (Box 482, Folder 1)
- New Jersey State AFL-CIO, Publication (Box 482, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Correspondence, 1971-1973 (Box 482, Folder 2)
- New Jersey State AFL-CIO, Publication (Box 482, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Correspondence, 1974-1978 (Box 482, Folder 3)
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations)., Publication (Box 482, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: New York State Official Directory: Union Made Products and Services -- Green Book, 1978; Publication (Box 482, Folder 4)
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations)., Publication (Box 482, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Constitution, 1983; Publication (Box 482, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: Constitution, 1987; Publication (Box 482, Folder 5)
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations)., Publication (Box 482, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: 1st Contract ends AFL-CIO Boycott of Lakewood Heaters, Fans, Tree Stands, 1995; Publication (Box 482, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: advertisement for the union, Publication (Box 482, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: Marshalltown Trowel Company added to don't buy, 1988; Publication (Box 482, Folder 6)
  - Item 4: Watch Americans making a better America, 1987; Publication (Box 482, Folder 6)
  - Item 5: AFL-CIO Union Industries Show - convention folder/info, 1987; Publication (Box 482, Folder 6)
  - Item 6: Song book, Publication (Box 482, Folder 6)
- New York State AFL-CIO, Publication (Box 482, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Legislative Bulletin, 1979; Publication (Box 482, Folder 7)
    Notes: Apr.-May (1979)
  - Item 2: Legislative Bulletin, 1980; Publication (Box 482, Folder 7)
    Notes: June (1980)
  - Item 3: Legislative Bulletin, 1981; Publication (Box 482, Folder 7)
    Notes: Feb. (1981)
  - Item 4: Correspondence - The NY State AFL-CIO's annual Legislative Conference will be held this year on Tues. Mar. 6, 1979; Publication (Box 482, Folder 7)
  - Item 5: 1978 New York State Legislature, Publication (Box 482, Folder 7)
    Notes: Roll call list
  - Item 6: Proceedings... COPE convention, 1994; Publication (Box 482, Folder 7)
  - Item 7: Priority Legislation, 1981; Publication (Box 482, Folder 7)
  - Item 8: Legislative Report, 1979; Publication (Box 482, Folder 7)
- New York State AFL-CIO, Publication (Box 482, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Constitution, 1988; Publication (Box 482, Folder 8)
  - Item 2: Constitution, 1992; Publication (Box 482, Folder 8)
- New Mexico State AFL-CIO, Publication (Box 482, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Constitution and by-laws, 1970; Publication (Box 482, Folder 9)
- New Jersey State AFL-CIO, Publication (Box 483, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Correspondence, 1979-1980 (Box 483, Folder 1)
- New Jersey State AFL-CIO, Publication (Box 483, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Correspondence, 1981-1983 (Box 483, Folder 2)
- New Jersey State AFL-CIO, Publication (Box 483, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Correspondence, 1984-1987 (Box 483, Folder 3)
- New Jersey State AFL-CIO, Publication (Box 483, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Correspondence, 1988-1989 (Box 483, Folder 4)
- New Jersey State AFL-CIO, Publication (Box 483, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Correspondence, 1990-1991 (Box 483, Folder 5)
- New Jersey State AFL-CIO, Publication (Box 483, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Correspondence, 1992-1993 (Box 483, Folder 6)
- New Jersey State AFL-CIO, Publication (Box 483, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Correspondence, 1994-1997 (Box 483, Folder 7)
- New York State AFL-CIO, Publication (Box 484, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: advertisement - Political Power - it's your hand, Publication (Box 484, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Substance abuse education and referral program, 1988; Publication (Box 484, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: A tribute to E. Howard Molisani, Secretary-Treasurer, 1987; Publication (Box 484, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Northeast Public Employees Conference - Conference flyer, 1992; Publication (Box 484, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: Community Services, 1988-1990 (Box 484, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: A Shop Stewards Guide, helping workers handle problems, 1988-1990 (Box 484, Folder 1)
  - Item 7: Invitation to the Presidents Reception, 1990; Publication (Box 484, Folder 1)
  - Item 8: Labor coordination program, 1988-1990 (Box 484, Folder 1)
  - Item 9: An alliance to promote the employment of individuals with disabilities, 1988-1990 (Box 484, Folder 1)
  - Item 10: A union response to alcohol and other drugs in the workplace, 1988-1990 (Box 484, Folder 1)
  - Item 11: Twenty-fifth Constitutional Convention - Program, 1988; Publication (Box 484, Folder 1)